- Mommy... I have a question for you.
- Okay.
- Would you rather go to Zapan, and have
lots of money and be rich and- and go to Zapan...
- Or do you want to have a son?
- You can be very rich! and go to Zapan!
but WITHOUT the option of having a son...
- If you want a son, you can't go to Zapan.
Do you get it? Or no?
- I got it. I can answer that question
very easily, you know?
- (No.)
- My answer is that I’d rather, a million times over,
have a son and be a mother to my boy...
- Than be rich, go to Japan,
go anywhere else... I don't care about those things!
- I’d never trade my son for all the money
in the WORLD! I'd never trade! Because MY son is the love of my life!
- (Got it.) What about you? Would you rather be
very rich and go to Japan...
- Where they have all that Pokémon stuff you love...
or would you rather have a mommy?
- Go to Zapan.